[{"answer": " I cant believe I lost Daves phone number!  Now how will I get home!", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Excuse me, mam.  Do you know if there are any buses around here that go t", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": " I cant believe I lost Daves phone number!  Now how will I get home!", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " What", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Excuse me, mam.  Do you know if there are any buses around here that go t", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Are there any bus stations around here that go to the east side", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " What", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Oh, sorry.  Not that I know of.  I dont ride the bus. Im pretty sure that there ar", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Are there any bus stations around here that go to the east side", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Where is that", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Oh, sorry.  Not that I know of.  I dont ride the bus. Im pretty sure that there ar", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Its about 30 blocks from here", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Where is that", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Oh, thats too far", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Its about 30 blocks from here", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": "Yeah, it would probably take you about 45 minutes to walk there", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Oh, thats too far", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " OK.  It looks like taking the bus is out of the picture.  Maybe I should take ", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Yeah, it would probably take you about 45 minutes to walk there", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Come again", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 37, "question": " OK.  It looks like taking the bus is out of the picture.  Maybe I should take ", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Are there any taxis around the mall here that I could take", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Come again", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Oh, taxis.  No, we dont have taxis around here", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Are there any taxis around the mall here that I could take", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Oh, I see", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Oh, taxis.  No, we dont have taxis around here", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Where exactly are you trying to go", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Oh, I see", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Im trying to get back to my apartment, which is on the east side of the city", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Where exactly are you trying to go", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Well, I think there are taxis somewhere around here.  You should check in th", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Im trying to get back to my apartment, which is on the east side of the city", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " OK, thanks!  Ill head over there right now", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Well, I think there are taxis somewhere around here.  You should check in th", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " No problem", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 48, "question": " OK, thanks!  Ill head over there right now", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Excuse me", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 52, "question": " No problem", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Yes, Can I help you", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Excuse me", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Yes, Im looking for the city maps", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Yes, Can I help you", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Theyre over in the back, right side corner of the store.  In the trave", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yes, Im looking for the city maps", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Thank you.  Do you know how long it would take to walk from the mall to th", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Theyre over in the back, right side corner of the store.  In the trave", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " To walk", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Thank you.  Do you know how long it would take to walk from the mall to th", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 64, "question": " To walk", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Hmmm.  Probably about an hour.  An hour and a half, maybe", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Yeah", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " But someone told me there were no taxi stands around here", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Hmmm.  Probably about an hour.  An hour and a half, maybe", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " No.  Theres one right outside the mall", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 71, "question": " But someone told me there were no taxi stands around here", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Oh, they must have been wrong.  Well, thats good news.  I can grab a taxi", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 72, "question": " No.  Theres one right outside the mall", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " No problem", "docId": "09-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Oh, they must have been wrong.  Well, thats good news.  I can grab a taxi", "qSentId": 75}]
